https://www.mltaikins.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - MLT Aikins - Western Canada's Law Firm
Client Resource Centre – COVID 19
.cls-rev-notag-1{fill:#fff;}.cls-rev-notag-2{fill:#cc1a42;}.cls-rev-notag-grey{fill:#808285}
MLT Aikins Website Privacy Policy
This website Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) outlines the information we, MLT Aikins LLP, may collect through use of this web site and any related sites (the “MLT Aikins Website”) and how such information may be used and disclosed. As practicing lawyers, we have professional and ethical obligations to maintain information we have received within our client relationships in confidence. This Privacy Policy supplements our applicable professional obligations of client confidentiality.
We do not collect personally identifiable information through the MLT Aikins Website unless such information is provided to us by email via a link contained on the MLT Aikins Website or submitted through a form, such as our contact form, online job application forms, or subscription form. It is important to note that any such communications are subject to the Terms of Use for the MLT Aikins Website.
We will only use such personally identifiable information for the purposes of responding to you, considering your application, and maintaining a record of your subscription and sending you requested updates.
We will not disclose to third parties any personally identifiable information collected by us through the MLT Aikins Website unless:
we have your consent;
we have a good faith belief that disclosure of the information is necessary to protect the rights or property of MLT Aikins; or
we are required by law to do so. You should also be aware that anonymous technical information may be collected by us as a result of your visit to the MLT Aikins Website. For example, this information may include your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring website addresses. We use this anonymous technical information for purposes such as improving the operation and content of the MLT Aikins Website and compiling aggregate and statistical information.
We will not attempt to link or match the anonymous technical information we collect with any personally-identifiable information unless:
we have your consent;
we (or our service providers) have detected or reasonably suspect any attempt to damage the MLT Aikins Website or other security breach; or
we are required by law to do so.
“Cookies” are small text files placed on your computer that can collect and store a variety of information. Permanent cookies are stored indefinitely on a user’s hard drive unless manually deleted, while temporary cookies are automatically deleted from the user’s browser upon logging out of a web site. Web browsers typically allow users to disable permanent and/or temporary cookies.
We may, from time to time, collect non-personal information about you and your use of the MLT Aikins Website through the use of cookies. We do not match or correlate this information with any personal information that you submit on the MLT Aikins Website.
The foregoing policy is effective as of January 1, 2017. MLT Aikins reserves the right to change this policy at any time.
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact Tamara Sinclair (tsinclair@mltaikins.com).
Winnipeg
Regina
Saskatoon
Calgary
Edmonton
Vancouver
“MLT Aikins”, the MLT Aikins Designs and “Western Canada’s Law Firm” are trademarks of MLT Aikins LLP. Copyright © 2017 MLT Aikins LLP. All rights reserved.
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Accessibility
Follow us on Twitter
Follow us on LinkedIn
Get MLT Aikins Updates
#Layer_1.mltnotags-1{fill:#231f20;}#Layer_1.mltnotags-2{fill:#c0022e;}}
.cls-rev-notag-1{fill:#fff;}.cls-rev-notag-2{fill:#cc1a42;}.cls-rev-notag-grey{fill:#808285}
